Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[The Tower of Whispers]
[برج الهمسات]
[Episode 22]
[الحلقة 22]
[Fengman House]
[بيت فنغمان]
Your Majesty, please leave here for now.
جلالتك، من فضلك اخرج من هنا الآن.
Just entrust Her Grace to me.
فقط أوكل نعمتها إليّ.
Just as I expected,
كما توقعت تمامًا،
the venomous worm is consuming your blood essence more rapidly.
الدودة السامة تستهلك جوهر دمك بسرعة أكبر.
Do you still have any Heart-Binding Poison?
هل لا يزال لديك أي سموم مرتبطة بالقلب؟
Yes, I do.
نعم أفعل.
But it took me 10 years
لكن الأمر استغرق مني 10 سنوات
to cultivate this venomous worm with blood essence.
لزراعة هذه الدودة السامة بجوهر الدم.
If you need it now,
إذا كنت بحاجة إليها الآن،
there isn't enough time.
ليس هناك وقت كافي .
Well, is there any way
حسنا، هل هناك أي طريقة
to cultivate it within a day?
لزراعته خلال يوم واحد؟
That's not okay.
هذا ليس جيدا.
In that way, it would accelerate the depletion of your body.
بهذه الطريقة، سوف يؤدي ذلك إلى تسريع استنزاف جسمك.
The consequences would be unimaginable.
وستكون العواقب لا يمكن تصورها.
So you mean
فهل تقصد
there is such a method?
هل هناك مثل هذه الطريقة؟
Sang Li, no matter what,
سانغ لي، بغض النظر عما يحدث،
I must give it a try.
يجب أن أحاول ذلك.
Sang Li.
سانج لي.
Tell me honestly,
أخبرني بصراحة
with my current health,
مع صحتي الحالية،
how much longer I can stay alive.
كم من الوقت يمكنني البقاء على قيد الحياة؟
You're like a lamp running out of its oil.
أنت مثل المصباح الذي ينفد زيته.
You may die within these few days.
ربما تموت خلال هذه الأيام القليلة.
I thought I could stay alive for a few more days.
اعتقدت أنني سأتمكن من البقاء على قيد الحياة لعدة أيام أخرى.
Sang Li.
سانج لي.
Regarding this matter,
وفيما يتعلق بهذا الأمر،
please don't tell Jun Che about it.
من فضلك لا تخبر جون تشي بهذا الأمر.
I'm afraid if he knows I'm dying,
أخشى أن يعلم أنني أموت،
he'll definitely go crazy again.
من المؤكد أنه سوف يصاب بالجنون مرة أخرى.
Even if I don't tell him now,
حتى لو لم أخبره الآن،
he would still go crazy.
لا زال يصاب بالجنون.
As soon as you pass away,
بمجرد وفاتك،
he would die with you immediately.
سيموت معك على الفور.
I have a way to ensure that
لدي طريقة للتأكد من ذلك
after I pass away,
بعد وفاتي،
he will no longer go crazy again.
لن يصاب بالجنون مرة أخرى.
Sang Li, please trust me one more time.
سانج لي، من فضلك ثق بي مرة أخرى.
At this point,
عند هذه النقطة،
no matter what you ask for, I'll say yes to you.
مهما كان ما تطلبه، سأقول لك نعم.
Sang Li.
سانج لي.
My brother has a straightforward personality
أخي لديه شخصية صريحة
and is inarticulate.
وهو غير قادر على التعبير.
But he is a very good person.
ولكنه شخص جيد جدًا.
Thank you, Your Grace.
شكرا لك يا صاحب السمو.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Her Grace is not seriously ill.
سموها ليست مريضة بشكل خطير.
She just needs to rest quietly.
إنها تحتاج فقط إلى الراحة بهدوء.
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
What's wrong, Your Majesty?
ما الأمر يا جلالتك؟
Don't call me Your Majesty.
لا تناديني بجلالتك.
Call me Five.
اتصل بي خمسة.
Well, Five,
حسنا، خمسة،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Just now, Sang Li insisted that I should go out.
قبل قليل، أصر سانج لي على أن أخرج.
I thought something bad had happened to you.
اعتقدت أن شيئًا سيئًا قد حدث لك.
Fortunately, you're not seriously ill.
لحسن الحظ، أنت لست مريضًا بشكل خطير.
If there had been bad news,
لو كانت هناك أخبار سيئة،
what would you do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
By searching the whole world,
من خلال البحث في جميع أنحاء العالم،
I don't believe I can't find the medicine to cure you.
لا أعتقد أنني لا أستطيع العثور على الدواء لعلاجك.
What if my fate is just like this,
ماذا لو كان مصيري مثل هذا؟
and it's hard to defy Heaven's will?
ومن الصعب مقاومة إرادة السماء؟
Then I'll go against Heaven.
ثم سأذهب ضد الجنة.
I'll sacrifice my own life.
سأضحي بحياتي.
If you're gone, it'll be meaningless for me to stay alive.
إذا رحلت، فلن يكون هناك معنى لبقائي على قيد الحياة.
I'd rather go to the netherworld with you.
أفضّل أن أذهب إلى العالم السفلي معك.
Anyway, you're not allowed to leave me.
على أية حال، ليس مسموحًا لك أن تتركني.
How long have I been teaching you?
منذ متى وأنا أعلمك؟
Why are you still so stubborn?
لماذا لا تزال عنيدًا جدًا؟
A leopard
نمر
cannot change its spots.
لا يمكن تغيير بقعه.
So you're despising me now?
إذن أنت تحتقرني الآن؟
How would I despise you, Five?
كيف أحتقرك يا فايف؟
I'm just joking.
انا امزح فقط
This joke of yours
هذه نكتتك
is really deadly to me.
إنه حقا مميت بالنسبة لي.
Your life has always belonged to me.
لقد كانت حياتك ملكي دائمًا.
However,
لكن،
besides your life,
بجانب حياتك،
I also want something else.
أريد شيئا آخر أيضا.
Since you became the emperor,
منذ أن أصبحت الإمبراطور،
we haven't gone out to have fun for a long time.
لم نخرج للاستمتاع منذ فترة طويلة.
After the court meetnig tomorrow,
بعد اجتماع المحكمة غدا،
can you have fun with me outside the palace?
هل يمكنك قضاء وقت ممتع معي خارج القصر؟
No.
لا.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
لم تتعافى بشكل كامل بعد.
I'm fine now.
أنا بخير الآن.
Keeping me confined won't help me get better.
إن إبقاءي محصوراً لن يساعدني على التحسن.
The answer is still no.
الجواب لا يزال لا .
The weather will be bad tomorrow.
الطقس سيكون سيئا غدا.
How can you know whether
كيف يمكنك أن تعرف ما إذا كان
tomorrow's weather will be fine or not?
هل سيكون الطقس غدا جميلا أم لا؟
In brief, for the foreseeable future,
باختصار، في المستقبل المنظور،
the weather will always be bad.
الطقس سيكون سيئا دائما
Then let's just wait till the weather becomes fine
إذن دعونا ننتظر حتى يصبح الطقس جميلا
before Your Majesty can come see me.
قبل أن يتمكن جلالتك من رؤيتي.
I understand.
أفهم.
Now Your Majesty's status is so noble
الآن أصبح وضع جلالتك نبيلًا جدًا
that we can't have fun in the marketplace anymore.
أننا لم نعد قادرين على الاستمتاع بالسوق بعد الآن.
I really can never defeat you.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع هزيمتك أبدًا.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
after you've rested well,
بعد أن حصلت على قسط جيد من الراحة،
and your health has improved a bit,
وتحسنت صحتك قليلا،
I'll take you out to have fun.
سأخرجك للاستمتاع.
♪ While the rain fades ♪
♪ بينما يتلاشى المطر ♪
♪ I wander once more through the old city upstream ♪
♪ أتجول مرة أخرى عبر المدينة القديمة أعلى النهر ♪
See if there's anything you like.
انظر إذا كان هناك أي شيء يعجبك.
♪ Yet I cannot erase ♪
♪ ولكن لا يمكنني أن أمحو ♪
♪ Mist-veiled tales that stir the river tides ♪
♪ حكايات غامضة تثير مد وجزر النهر ♪
♪ In fading dreams ♪
♪ في الأحلام الباهتة ♪
♪ Lanterns stain the worldly bustle with their glow ♪
♪ الفوانيس تلطخ صخب العالم بتوهجها ♪
♪ Today's tales sound off-key and hollow ♪
♪ حكايات اليوم تبدو غير متناغمة وجوفاء ♪
How beautiful.
كم هو جميل.
♪ Distorted, or left in fragments ♪
♪ مشوهة، أو متبقية في شظايا ♪
♪ I heard the legends rise like the wind ♪
♪ سمعت الأساطير ترتفع مثل الريح ♪
[Protect the Country and the People]
[حماية البلاد والشعب]
♪ Only to fall back into nothingness ♪
♪ فقط للسقوط مرة أخرى في العدم ♪
♪ I dare not disturb the toll of the bell ♪
♪ لا أجرؤ على إزعاج قرع الجرس ♪
[Imperial Guangji Temple]
[معبد غوانغجي الإمبراطوري]
♪ Nor dare I awaken the dream ♪
♪ ولا أجرؤ على إيقاظ الحلم ♪
♪ Fearing the retelling ♪
♪ خوفا من إعادة السرد ♪
♪ Could never capture that breathtaking glance back then ♪
♪ لم أستطع أبدًا التقاط تلك النظرة المذهلة في ذلك الوقت ♪
♪ Loving you was devotion beneath moon and breeze ♪
♪ حبك كان إخلاصًا تحت القمر والنسيم ♪
♪ Both ordinary love and hate ♪
♪ الحب والكراهية العاديين ♪
♪ Thus the era was shaken ♪
♪ وهكذا اهتز العصر ♪
♪ In youthful years of innocence ♪
♪ في سنوات الشباب من البراءة ♪
[Imperial Guangji Temple]
[معبد غوانغجي الإمبراطوري]
♪ When meetings would not come again ♪
♪ عندما لا تعود الاجتماعات مرة أخرى ♪
♪ The mortal realm was bound to start yet never end ♪
♪ كان من المفترض أن يبدأ عالم البشر ولكن لن ينتهي أبدًا ♪
♪ I heard that in the spring of '64 ♪
♪ سمعت ذلك في ربيع عام 1964 ♪
♪ The wind rose at the mountain gate ♪
♪ ارتفعت الريح عند بوابة الجبل ♪
♪ Strange tales unfold in a book ♪
♪ حكايات غريبة تتكشف في كتاب ♪
What are you writing?
ماذا تكتب؟
♪ Recording their story ♪
♪ تسجيل قصتهم ♪
Don't peek at it.
لا تنظر إليه.
♪ Ridiculous words ♪
♪ كلمات سخيفة ♪
♪ Hastily blaming the cruelty of time ♪
♪ إلقاء اللوم على قسوة الزمن على عجل ♪
♪ Yet it still knocks on my heart and soul ♪
♪ ومع ذلك لا يزال يطرق على قلبي وروحى ♪
♪ Like a dream from another life ♪
♪ مثل حلم من حياة أخرى ♪
♪ Reincarnating in words ♪
♪ التناسخ في الكلمات ♪
♪ Afraid others won't understand ♪
♪ خائف من أن الآخرين لن يفهموا ♪
♪ Afraid of stirring emotions for no reason ♪
♪ خائف من إثارة المشاعر بدون سبب ♪
♪ Better to have a beginning with no end ♪
♪ من الأفضل أن تكون البداية بلا نهاية ♪
[The Great Buddha's Hall]
[قاعة بوذا العظيم]
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
I've told you before
لقد قلت لك من قبل
it's better to trust me than to trust them.
من الأفضل أن تثق بي بدلاً من أن تثق بهم.
Five.
خمسة.
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث هراء.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then I'll wait for you outside.
سأنتظرك بالخارج إذن.
Yingying.
ينغ ينغ.
I'll help you
سأساعدك
fulfill your wish.
تحقيق رغبتك.
Miss!
يفتقد!
Miss, what's wrong?
آنسة، ما الأمر؟
Yingying!
ينغ ينغ!
I'll go ask for help.
سأذهب لطلب المساعدة.
Yingying, you'll be fine.
ينغ ينغ، سوف تكوني بخير.
I'll take you back to the palace.
سأعيدك إلى القصر.
Let's go find Sang Li.
دعونا نذهب للبحث عن سانغ لي.
Let's go find the imperial doctors.
دعونا نذهب للبحث عن الأطباء الإمبراطوريين.
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
I can't walk anymore.
لم أعد أستطيع المشي بعد الآن.
Well...
حسنًا...
Just drink some of my blood.
فقط اشرب بعضًا من دمي.
My blood can help to heal wounds.
دمي يمكن أن يساعد في شفاء الجروح.
I want you to talk with me.
أريدك أن تتحدث معي.
Let me tell you a secret.
دعني أخبرك بسر.
I've experienced
لقد مررت بتجربة
the same lifetime twice.
نفس الحياة مرتين.
This is my second life now.
هذه هي حياتي الثانية الآن.
In my previous life,
في حياتي السابقة،
during the Lantern Festival in the 28th year of Tianchen,
خلال مهرجان الفوانيس في السنة الثامنة والعشرين من تيانتشين،
my father was framed by Ding Huairen and put into prison.
لقد تم القبض على والدي من قبل دينغ هوايرين وتم إرساله إلى السجن.
After that, I lost all my family one after another.
وبعد ذلك فقدت عائلتي كلها واحدا تلو الآخر.
That's why I hate Ding Huairen so much.
لهذا السبب أكره دينغ هوايرين كثيرًا.
Did we know each other in your previous life?
هل عرفنا بعضنا البعض في حياتك السابقة؟
Yes, we did.
نعم لقد فعلنا ذلك.
In my previous life,
في حياتي السابقة،
you were a tyrant,
لقد كنت طاغية
and I was your consort.
وكنت زوجتك.
You accidentally stabbed me,
لقد طعنتني عن طريق الخطأ،
and I died because of that.
ومت بسبب ذلك.
No wonder when you first met me,
لا عجب عندما التقيت بي لأول مرة،
you used those little tricks to bully me and vent your anger.
لقد استخدمت تلك الحيل الصغيرة لتخويفني والتنفيس عن غضبك.
I'm sorry, Five.
أنا آسف، خمسة.
That's because in my previous life,
هذا لأنه في حياتي السابقة،
you were so detestable.
لقد كنت بغيضًا جدًا.
No, there's no need to apologize.
لا، ليست هناك حاجة للاعتذار.
You thought I was detestable,
لقد ظننت أنني بغيض،
and that was all my fault.
وكان هذا كله خطئي.
Five.
خمسة.
I know you like how I'm
أنا أعلم أنك تحبني كما أنا
so enterprising
مغامر جدا
and capable.
وقادرة.
But I wasn't like that at first.
ولكنني لم أكن كذلك في البداية.
At that time,
في ذلك الوقت،
I was such a coward.
لقد كنت جبانًا جدًا.
That's why in this life,
ولهذا السبب في هذه الحياة،
I want to change myself so desperately.
أريد أن أغير نفسي بشدة.
No, Yingying.
لا، ينجينج.
What I like
ما يعجبني
is every aspect of you,
هو كل جانب منك،
the one who took me to eat sugar figurines
الذي أخذني لأكل تماثيل السكر
and watch fireworks.
ومشاهدة الألعاب النارية.
I like all your mundane wishes.
أنا أحب جميع رغباتك الدنيوية.
As long as I remain who I am,
طالما بقيت كما أنا،
no matter how many more lifetimes pass,
بغض النظر عن عدد الأعمار التي مرت،
I will always love you.
سأحبك دائما.
It's just that I'm lucky enough in this life.
إنني محظوظة جدًا في هذه الحياة.
Coincidentally,
بالمصادفة،
you love me, too.
أنت تحبني أيضا.
Five.
خمسة.
Yingying!
ينغ ينغ!